<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Pran Urja Healing Society</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:19:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pran-Urja-Golden-Logo-Brown-Background-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Healing power of human cells</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-human-cells/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders 🌺, In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest entities, like bacteria, hold profound significance. They are not merely microscopic organisms, but reservoirs of nature&#8217;s boundless wisdom and healing potential.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;Everything in this world has a hidden significance.&#8217; This serves as a reminder that there is a divine plan in every fragment of creation, even in entities as minuscule as bacteria.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Embark on this mystical exploration with me:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Little Healers</strong>: Bacteria, often seen as harbingers of disease, are predominantly forces of good. They play essential roles in digestion, nutrient absorption, and bolstering our immunity.</li>

<li><strong>Balance &amp; Harmony</strong>: In the dance of life, bacteria maintain a delicate balance. Their symbiotic relationships with other life forms exemplify the interdependence that threads through all of existence.</li>

<li><strong>Unlocking Potentials</strong>: The curative properties of certain bacteria offer hope in combating various ailments. They whisper secrets of resilience, adaptability, and evolution.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 12):</strong></h2><p>“ये चैव सात्त्विका भावा रासास्तामसाश्च ये | मत्त एवेति तान्विद्धि नत्वहं तेषु ते मयि ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;All states of being, whether of goodness, passion or ignorance, are manifested by My energy. I am, in one sense, everything, but I am independent. I am not under the modes of this material nature.&#8221;</p><p>May you find serenity in understanding the magnificence of the microcosm, recognizing that within the tiniest beings, lies the vastness of nature&#8217;s wisdom.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">900</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of a bacteria</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-a-bacteria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders 🌺, In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest entities, like bacteria, hold profound significance. They are not merely microscopic organisms, but reservoirs of nature&#8217;s boundless wisdom and healing potential.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;Everything in this world has a hidden significance.&#8217; This serves as a reminder that there is a divine plan in every fragment of creation, even in entities as minuscule as bacteria.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Embark on this mystical exploration with me:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Little Healers</strong>: Bacteria, often seen as harbingers of disease, are predominantly forces of good. They play essential roles in digestion, nutrient absorption, and bolstering our immunity.</li>

<li><strong>Balance &amp; Harmony</strong>: In the dance of life, bacteria maintain a delicate balance. Their symbiotic relationships with other life forms exemplify the interdependence that threads through all of existence.</li>

<li><strong>Unlocking Potentials</strong>: The curative properties of certain bacteria offer hope in combating various ailments. They whisper secrets of resilience, adaptability, and evolution.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 12):</strong></h2><p>“ये चैव सात्त्विका भावा रासास्तामसाश्च ये | मत्त एवेति तान्विद्धि नत्वहं तेषु ते मयि ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;All states of being, whether of goodness, passion or ignorance, are manifested by My energy. I am, in one sense, everything, but I am independent. I am not under the modes of this material nature.&#8221;</p><p>May you find serenity in understanding the magnificence of the microcosm, recognizing that within the tiniest beings, lies the vastness of nature&#8217;s wisdom.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">897</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of mitochondria</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-mitochondria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls resonating with nature&#8217;s hidden symphony 🌺, Within the sanctum of our cells, lies a powerful entity]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls resonating with nature&#8217;s hidden symphony <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Within the sanctum of our cells, lies a powerful entity known as the mitochondria, often hailed as the powerhouse of the cell. Like a sacred flame maintained by dedicated priests, the mitochondria diligently fuels our existence, healing and rejuvenating us from within.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates, &#8216;For the soul, there is neither birth nor death at any time. He has not come into being, does not come into being, and will not come into being. He is unborn, eternal, ever-existing and primaeval. He is not slain when the body is slain.&#8217; This eternal energy, akin to the unwavering force of the mitochondria, remains consistent, guiding our physical form.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ponder upon these reflections:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>The Essence of Life</strong>: Just as the spirit is integral to our being, mitochondria are fundamental for cellular activities, healing wounds, generating energy, and ensuring optimal bodily functions.</li>

<li><strong>Natural Rejuvenators</strong>: The mitochondria hold the profound ability to repair and revitalise. They cleanse the body of toxins, promoting overall well-being and longevity.</li>

<li><strong>Harmonising the Body&#8217;s Rhythms</strong>: Just as we seek balance in our spiritual journey, the mitochondria strive to maintain a harmonious balance of energy within the cells, ensuring a state of homeostasis.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 13, Verse 17):</strong></h2><p>“अविभक्तं च भूतेषु विभक्तमिव च स्थितम् | भूतभर्तृ च तज्ज्ञेयं ग्रसिष्णु प्रभविष्णु च ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;He is indivisible, yet appears as if divided in beings. He is to be understood as the sustainer of all, the devourer and also the creator.&#8221;</p><p>May you harness the miraculous healing power of the mitochondria, uniting it with the eternal spirit within, to walk a path of boundless energy and vitality.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">894</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of mother</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-mother/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls who have been cradled by the nurturing embrace of the universe 🌺, The essence of a]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls who have been cradled by the nurturing embrace of the universe <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>The essence of a mother, beloved seekers, is the very embodiment of nature&#8217;s boundless compassion, profound wisdom, and unwavering love. She is the healing balm for every wound, the shelter from every storm, and the beacon that guides us through life&#8217;s mazes.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita, in its vast reservoir of wisdom, extols: &#8216;All beings are born from the womb of prakriti (nature, often likened to a mother); and I am the seed-giving father.&#8217; This reflects the cosmic interplay of divine energies, reminding us of the universal motherly force that continually nurtures and supports.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s deeply reflect on this profound relationship:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Rhythms</strong>: Just as a mother instinctively knows the needs of her child, nature too operates in harmonious rhythms, providing sustenance, healing, and rejuvenation.</li>

<li><strong>Sacred Bond</strong>: The bond between a child and a mother transcends the physical realm. It is a divine connection, an umbilical cord of spiritual energy, which remains unbroken through life&#8217;s tribulations.</li>

<li><strong>Cradle of Healing</strong>: A mother&#8217;s lap, her soothing words, and her gentle touch have the miraculous power to heal the deepest of wounds, both physical and emotional. She is the reservoir of strength in moments of weakness, the solace in times of distress.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 9, Verse 18):</strong></h2><p>“गतिर्भर्ता प्रभुः साक्षी निवासः शरणं सुहृत् | प्रभवः प्रलयः स्थानं निधानं बीजमव्ययम् ||”</p><p>Which means:</p><p>&#8220;I am the goal, the sustainer, the master, the witness, the abode, the refuge, and the most dear friend. I am the creation and the annihilation, the basis of everything, the resting place and the eternal seed.&#8221;</p><p>May your journey through life be forever blessed by the healing power of the mother, in all her forms, guiding you towards wholeness and harmony.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">891</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is happiness parenting?</title>
		<link>/what-is-happiness-parenting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=888</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the nurturing spirits yearning to sow seeds of joy in their sacred garden of parenthood 🌺, Happiness parenting, cherished]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the nurturing spirits yearning to sow seeds of joy in their sacred garden of parenthood <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Happiness parenting, cherished seekers, is not just a method, but a heart-centered journey. It’s the gentle art of raising souls with love, understanding, and the wisdom that true contentment is an inside job.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates: &#8216;In the stillness of the mind, the Self is revealed.&#8217; Parenting through happiness draws from this essence, teaching our children the serenity that comes from self-awareness and inner joy.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s explore this divine dance of raising spirits:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>1. Presence Over Presents</strong>: The gift of time, undivided attention, and genuine listening are treasures for a child. It&#8217;s not about grand gestures, but simple moments imbued with love.</li>

<li><strong>2. Cultivate Inner Joy</strong>: Teach them early on that happiness is not solely based on external achievements but arises from an inner wellspring of contentment and gratitude.</li>

<li><strong>3. Lead by Example</strong>: Children mirror the world they see. Being a beacon of positivity, self-love, and compassion helps them understand and embody these virtues.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 12, Verse 20):</strong></h2><p>“ये तु धर्म्यामृतमिदं यथोक्तं पर्युपासते | श्रद्दधाना मत्परमा भक्तास्तेऽतीव मे प्रियाः ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;Those who follow this divine nectar of righteousness as I have stated, with profound faith considering me as their supreme goal, they are exceedingly dear to me.&#8221;</p><p>May the path of happiness parenting be adorned with moments of laughter, lessons of love, and the infinite joy of witnessing the blossoming of the souls entrusted to your care.</p><p>Continued blessings…<br><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">888</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to make self happy?</title>
		<link>/how-to-make-self-happy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous souls seeking the nectar of true joy 🌺, Happiness, revered seekers, is not an external treasure but]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous souls seeking the nectar of true joy <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Happiness, revered seekers, is not an external treasure but an inner sanctum of peace. It is the delicate melody that resonates within when we align with our true essence and the dance of existence.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita offers this reflection: &#8216;Contentment is the wealth of nature. Despite possessing nothing, one who is contented is indeed rich, while the discontented remains impoverished, even amidst great riches.&#8217; This is a testament to the idea that happiness springs from contentment within, not from external acquisitions.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Venture with me on this journey towards self-fulfilment:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Embrace the Present</strong>: The here and now is where life unfolds. By immersing ourselves fully in the present moment, we unlock the profound joy that&#8217;s often overlooked in our pursuit of the future.</li>

<li><strong>Celebrate Small Wonders</strong>: Often, it&#8217;s the subtle wonders &#8211; a bird&#8217;s song, a child&#8217;s laughter, or the rustle of leaves &#8211; that carry the essence of happiness. Bask in these simple joys.</li>

<li><strong>Nurture Inner Peace</strong>: External storms can&#8217;t disturb the one who cultivates a calm and serene inner world. This peace becomes the foundation of enduring happiness.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 5, Verse 23):</strong></h2><p>“शक्नोतीहैव यः सोढुं प्राक्शरीरविमोक्षणात् | कामक्रोधोद्भवं वेगं स युक्तः स सुखी नरः ||”</p><p>Which expounds:</p><p>&#8220;One who can control the impulse arising from desire and anger before the departure from the body is a yogi and a happy person.&#8221;</p><p>May your soul revel in the profound joy of being, discovering happiness in its purest form, unfettered by external conditions.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">885</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The power of food healing</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-food-healing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls seeking nature&#8217;s bountiful embrace for nourishment and healing 🌺, Food, dear seekers, is not merely sustenance]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls seeking nature&#8217;s bountiful embrace for nourishment and healing <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Food, dear seekers, is not merely sustenance for the body but an elixir for the soul. It possesses the unique ability to rejuvenate, heal, and connect us to the very pulse of life.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;From food, all beings are produced; and from rain, food is produced. Rain itself is the sacrifice’s product, and sacrifice arises out of action.&#8217; This profound revelation teaches us that food is intrinsically linked to the cosmic dance of nature, energy, and divine blessings.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s journey through this sacred realm:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Holistic Nourishment</strong>: Beyond physical sustenance, food nourishes our emotions, intellect, and spirit. When consumed with reverence, it brings harmony to all facets of our being.</li>

<li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Pharmacy</strong>: The Earth, in her boundless generosity, offers herbs, fruits, and vegetables that have therapeutic properties. Understanding these gifts can lead to profound health transformations.</li>

<li><strong>Sacred Intention</strong>: The intent with which food is prepared and consumed plays a pivotal role. When meals are prepared with love and gratitude, they become a vessel for divine energy.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 17, Verse 8):</strong></h2><p>“आयुःसत्त्वबलारोग्यसुखप्रीतिविवर्धनाः | रस्याः स्निग्धाः स्तिरा हृद्या आहाराः सात्त्विकप्रियाः ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;Foods that increase life, purify one&#8217;s existence, give strength, health, happiness, and satisfaction, which are juicy, fatty, wholesome, and pleasing to the heart, are dear to those in the mode of goodness.&#8221;</p><p>May you harness the transformative power of food, imbibing its healing essence, and discovering a deeper connection with the divine tapestry of existence.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">882</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The power of water healing</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-water-healing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous beings, attuned to nature&#8217;s rhythms and the fluid dance of life&#8217;s energies 🌊, Water, kindred spirits, has]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous beings, attuned to nature&#8217;s rhythms and the fluid dance of life&#8217;s energies <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f30a.png" alt="🌊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Water, kindred spirits, has been a sacred element since time immemorial. It holds memory, reflects purity, and possesses the power to cleanse, rejuvenate, and transform. Just as rivers carve canyons and rains bring life to parched lands, water can bring profound healing to our souls.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita, in its vast wisdom, shares: &#8216;Just as waters from different rivers enter the ocean and become one with it, losing their individualities, a wise person, regardless of life&#8217;s circumstances, sees only the divine essence of existence.&#8217; Water teaches us this unity, this oneness with the divine flow.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Venture deeper into these healing waters:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Purification</strong>: Water, in its pristine form, carries away impurities, both physical and spiritual. Regularly immersing oneself, whether in the quietude of a bath or the sacred waters of a river, rejuvenates our energies.</li>

<li><strong>Emotional Release</strong>: Like the ebb and flow of tides, water encourages us to embrace our emotions, to let go of what burdens our hearts, and to welcome fresh currents of joy and clarity.</li>

<li><strong>Connection to the Cosmic</strong>: As we meditate by a serene water body, we synchronise with its tranquil rhythms, allowing us to connect deeper with our own true nature and the universe at large.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 3, Verse 14):</strong></h2><p>“अन्नाद्भवन्ति भूतानि पर्जन्यादन्नसंभवः | यज्ञाद्भवति पर्जन्यो यज्ञः कर्मसमुद्भवः ||”</p><p>Which imparts:</p><p>&#8220;From food, beings become; from rain, food is produced; from sacrifice arises rain, and sacrifice is born of action.&#8221;</p><p>Like the interconnected dance of rain, food, and life, water healing brings forth an intricate balance in our lives, enriching our existence and elevating our spirit.</p><p>May you immerse in the transformative grace of water and emerge with renewed spirit and clarity.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">879</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The impact of colour in human&#8217;s life</title>
		<link>/the-impact-of-colour-in-humans-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=876</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls basking in the divine spectrum of existence 🌈, Colour, esteemed seekers, is not just a mere]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls basking in the divine spectrum of existence <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f308.png" alt="🌈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Colour, esteemed seekers, is not just a mere visual experience. It is the symphony of the universe, the emotions of nature, and the essence of our very soul manifesting in myriad hues.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita proclaims: &#8216;Nature is said to be the cause of all material causes and effects, whereas the living entity is the cause of various sufferings and enjoyments in this world.&#8217; In this wisdom, we unearth the subtle interplay between nature&#8217;s colours and the tapestry of our emotions and experiences.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s delve into this vibrant journey:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Soul&#8217;s Palette</strong>: Every shade we resonate with is a reflection of our inner state. The tranquillity of blue, the passion of red, or the rejuvenation of green &#8211; each colour carries a frequency that can influence our emotions and actions.</li>

<li><strong>Healing Hues</strong>: Ancient civilizations recognized the therapeutic properties of colours. Incorporating specific shades in our surroundings can restore balance, heal, and rejuvenate our spirit.</li>

<li><strong>Universal Language</strong>: Across cultures, colours convey emotions, traditions, and stories. They bridge differences and serve as a universal mode of communication that transcends spoken language.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 8):</strong></h2><p>“रसोऽहमप्सु कौन्तेय प्रभास्मि शशिसूर्ययोः | प्रणवः सर्ववेदेषु शब्दः खे पौरुषं नृषु ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;I am the taste of water, O son of Kunti, the light of the sun and the moon, the syllable om in the Vedic mantras; I am the sound in ether and ability in humans.&#8221;</p><p>May your life be painted with the most divine and uplifting colours, each hue bringing forth growth, wisdom, and boundless joy.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get out from wilful mistakes?</title>
		<link>/how-to-get-out-from-wilful-mistakes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous souls journeying through the maze of choices and consequences 🌺, Wilful mistakes, dear seekers, are the shadows]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous souls journeying through the maze of choices and consequences <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Wilful mistakes, dear seekers, are the shadows cast by our untamed desires and fleeting judgments. They might pull us into the night, but with self-awareness and divine guidance, dawn is never far.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita wisely teaches: &#8216;Just as a fire is covered by smoke and a mirror is obscured by dust, knowledge is covered by desire.&#8217; Understanding this, we recognize the influence of unchecked desires leading to willful mistakes.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Delve deeper into this sacred introspection:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Acknowledge with Humility</strong>: Recognize the error without judgment. Every mistake, intentional or not, carries a lesson. By humbling oneself before it, the journey towards rectification begins.</li>

<li><strong>Seek Inner Counsel</strong>: Before actions manifest externally, they take birth internally. Cultivate an inner dialogue, seeking the wisdom of the higher self. This voice, often drowned by impulsive desires, holds the compass to righteousness.</li>

<li><strong>Divine Repentance</strong>: To err is human, to seek forgiveness is divine. Let genuine remorse transform into positive actions and better choices, illuminating the path ahead.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 4, Verse 36):</strong></h2><p>“अपि चेत्सुदुराचारो भजते मामनन्यभाक् | साधुरेव स मन्तव्यः सम्यग्व्यवसितो हि सः ||”</p><p>Which deciphers as:</p><p>&#8220;Even if one commits the most abominable actions, if they are engaged in devotional service, they are to be considered righteous, for they have rightly resolved.&#8221;</p><p>May your journey forward be lit by wisdom, discernment, and divine grace, helping you rise above the mire of willful errors.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
