<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sacred Verses Unveiled &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/sacred-verses-unveiled/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Pran Urja Healing Society</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:37:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pran-Urja-Golden-Logo-Brown-Background-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Sacred Verses Unveiled &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shri Vishnu Stuti &#8211; A Deep Dive into the Ocean of Devotion</title>
		<link>/shri-vishnu-stuti-a-deep-dive-into-the-ocean-of-devotion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sacred Verses Unveiled]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introduction Welcome, dear soul, to the sacred sanctuary where every word penned down is a petal offered at the lotus]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Introduction</h3><p>Welcome, dear soul, to the sacred sanctuary where every word penned down is a petal offered at the lotus feet of the Divine. Today, we start our elevating journey through the resplendent verses of &#8220;<strong>Shri Vishnu Stuti.</strong>&#8221; This eternal divine hymn serves as both a celebration and invocation of <strong>God Shri Vishnu</strong>, the <strong>Preserver</strong> in the Divine Trinity. Each verse, a woven garland of Sanskrit syllables, carries the aroma of timeless devotion and infinite wisdom. Let these words not just be read but be absorbed, so they echo in the inner corridors of your heart, where God Shri Vishnu resides.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading">Vishnu Stuti &#8211; Vishnushodashanamani Meaning with Interpretation by Sri Guru Vyas</h2><h3 class="wp-block-heading">First Section: Invocation for Removing Obstacles</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio">शुक्लाम्बरधरं विष्णुं शशिवर्णं चतुर्भुजम्,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio">प्रसन्नवदनं ध्यायेत् सर्वविघ्नोपशान्तये।</h4></blockquote><p>In this opening verse, the divine form of God Shri Vishnu is presented as wearing pure white garments, signifying purity and holiness. His complexion shines like the moon, embodying tranquility. With four arms, he holds the power to protect us in all directions. His face wears an eternally joyous smile, giving us reassurance. By meditating on this divine form, all obstacles and challenges in life will be erased. This verse sets the tone for beginning any endeavor without hindrances.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Second Section: Attributes of God Shri Vishnu</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">शान्ताकारं भुजगशयनं पद्मनाभं सुरेशं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">विश्वाधारं गगनसदृशं मेघवर्ण शुभाङ्गम्।</h4></blockquote><p>Here, we delve deeper into the qualities and grandeur of God Shri Vishnu. His form is peaceful, embodying the essence of tranquility that can soothe any troubled heart. He reclines on the serpent Adi Shesha, representing the universe&#8217;s unending cycles of creation and dissolution. His navel blooms a lotus, the eternal source of all creation. As the Lord of lords, he governs the cosmic laws. His expansive form is limitless like the sky. The color of his skin resembles a dark rain cloud, emphasizing the life-giving and sustaining aspects of his divinity.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Third Section: God Shri Vishnu in Daily Life</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">औषधे चिंतये विष्णुम भोजने च जनार्धनम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">शयने पद्मनाभं च विवाहे च प्रजापतिम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">युद्धे चक्रधरम देवं प्रवासे च त्रिविक्रमं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">नारायणं तनु त्यागे श्रीधरं प्रिय संगमे,</h4></blockquote><p>The shloka urges us to remember God Shri Vishnu throughout various moments in our daily life. When taking medicine, think of him as the healer. While eating, remember him as the sustainer. At bedtime, see him as the comforter. During marriage, he is the eternal matchmaker. In battle, he&#8217;s our protector. During travel, he&#8217;s the guide. In the face of death, he&#8217;s the eternal soul. And in times of love and unity, he is the embodiment of all relationships.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Fourth Section: God Shri Vishnu in Challenges</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">दुःस्वप्ने स्मर गोविन्दम संकटे मधुसूधनम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">कानने नारासिम्हम च पावके जलाशयिनाम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">जलमध्ये वराहम च पर्वते रघु नन्दनं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">गमने वामनं चैव सर्व कार्येशु माधवं।</h4></blockquote><p>In times of distress or trouble, each form of God Shri Vishnu comes as a guide, a savior, or a protector. Whether it&#8217;s a bad dream, life challenges, dangerous forests, or perils by fire, each avatar has a specific role. Remembering these forms in specific circumstances can offer comfort and solutions.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Final Section: The Fruit of Devotion</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">षोडशैतानी नमानी प्रातरुत्थाय यह पठेत,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">सर्वपापा विर्निमुक्तो विष्णुलोके महीयते।</h4></blockquote><p>Reciting these sixteen names of God Shri Vishnu early in the morning washes away all sins and bestows a high place in Vishnuloka, his eternal abode.</p><p>Incorporate these verses into your daily life. Each time you chant or even think of them, it&#8217;s like sending a personal invitation to God Shri Vishnu to walk alongside you. And what&#8217;s more reassuring than knowing the divine is by your side, guiding, protecting, and loving you in every moment of life?</p><figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Vishnustuti- Vishnushodashanamani" width="500" height="375" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kRPMyg1xhCA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>This hymn is not merely a combination of words and syllables but an intimate conversation between you and the Divine.</strong></h2><p><strong>It serves as a lighthouse guiding you through the murky waters of life&#8217;s challenges, illuminating your path with the divine glow of God Shri Vishnu&#8217;s love, wisdom, and protection.</strong> </p><p>May your life be filled with the boundless grace of God Shri Vishnu, and may you find solace, strength, and eternal joy in these divine verses. Here, your diary closes, but the dialogue with the Divine continues forever. With a heart full of devotion and a soul touched by the divine, walk forth in life, knowing that you&#8217;re never alone; for in every step, God Shri Vishnu walks with you.</p><p>&#8211; <strong>Sri Guru Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society,<br>Jodhpur (Rajasthan) &#8211; 342003</p><p></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1486</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
