<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sri Guru Baba Vyas &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/divyanshu_dtnkfkt9/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Pran Urja Healing Society</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:37:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pran-Urja-Golden-Logo-Brown-Background-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Sri Guru Baba Vyas &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Healing power of human cells</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-human-cells/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders 🌺, In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest entities, like bacteria, hold profound significance. They are not merely microscopic organisms, but reservoirs of nature&#8217;s boundless wisdom and healing potential.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;Everything in this world has a hidden significance.&#8217; This serves as a reminder that there is a divine plan in every fragment of creation, even in entities as minuscule as bacteria.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Embark on this mystical exploration with me:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Little Healers</strong>: Bacteria, often seen as harbingers of disease, are predominantly forces of good. They play essential roles in digestion, nutrient absorption, and bolstering our immunity.</li>

<li><strong>Balance &amp; Harmony</strong>: In the dance of life, bacteria maintain a delicate balance. Their symbiotic relationships with other life forms exemplify the interdependence that threads through all of existence.</li>

<li><strong>Unlocking Potentials</strong>: The curative properties of certain bacteria offer hope in combating various ailments. They whisper secrets of resilience, adaptability, and evolution.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 12):</strong></h2><p>“ये चैव सात्त्विका भावा रासास्तामसाश्च ये | मत्त एवेति तान्विद्धि नत्वहं तेषु ते मयि ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;All states of being, whether of goodness, passion or ignorance, are manifested by My energy. I am, in one sense, everything, but I am independent. I am not under the modes of this material nature.&#8221;</p><p>May you find serenity in understanding the magnificence of the microcosm, recognizing that within the tiniest beings, lies the vastness of nature&#8217;s wisdom.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">900</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of a bacteria</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-a-bacteria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders 🌺, In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the awakened souls seeking harmony in nature&#8217;s smallest wonders <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>In the vast tapestry of creation, even the tiniest entities, like bacteria, hold profound significance. They are not merely microscopic organisms, but reservoirs of nature&#8217;s boundless wisdom and healing potential.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;Everything in this world has a hidden significance.&#8217; This serves as a reminder that there is a divine plan in every fragment of creation, even in entities as minuscule as bacteria.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Embark on this mystical exploration with me:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Little Healers</strong>: Bacteria, often seen as harbingers of disease, are predominantly forces of good. They play essential roles in digestion, nutrient absorption, and bolstering our immunity.</li>

<li><strong>Balance &amp; Harmony</strong>: In the dance of life, bacteria maintain a delicate balance. Their symbiotic relationships with other life forms exemplify the interdependence that threads through all of existence.</li>

<li><strong>Unlocking Potentials</strong>: The curative properties of certain bacteria offer hope in combating various ailments. They whisper secrets of resilience, adaptability, and evolution.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 12):</strong></h2><p>“ये चैव सात्त्विका भावा रासास्तामसाश्च ये | मत्त एवेति तान्विद्धि नत्वहं तेषु ते मयि ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;All states of being, whether of goodness, passion or ignorance, are manifested by My energy. I am, in one sense, everything, but I am independent. I am not under the modes of this material nature.&#8221;</p><p>May you find serenity in understanding the magnificence of the microcosm, recognizing that within the tiniest beings, lies the vastness of nature&#8217;s wisdom.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">897</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of mitochondria</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-mitochondria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls resonating with nature&#8217;s hidden symphony 🌺, Within the sanctum of our cells, lies a powerful entity]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls resonating with nature&#8217;s hidden symphony <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Within the sanctum of our cells, lies a powerful entity known as the mitochondria, often hailed as the powerhouse of the cell. Like a sacred flame maintained by dedicated priests, the mitochondria diligently fuels our existence, healing and rejuvenating us from within.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates, &#8216;For the soul, there is neither birth nor death at any time. He has not come into being, does not come into being, and will not come into being. He is unborn, eternal, ever-existing and primaeval. He is not slain when the body is slain.&#8217; This eternal energy, akin to the unwavering force of the mitochondria, remains consistent, guiding our physical form.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ponder upon these reflections:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>The Essence of Life</strong>: Just as the spirit is integral to our being, mitochondria are fundamental for cellular activities, healing wounds, generating energy, and ensuring optimal bodily functions.</li>

<li><strong>Natural Rejuvenators</strong>: The mitochondria hold the profound ability to repair and revitalise. They cleanse the body of toxins, promoting overall well-being and longevity.</li>

<li><strong>Harmonising the Body&#8217;s Rhythms</strong>: Just as we seek balance in our spiritual journey, the mitochondria strive to maintain a harmonious balance of energy within the cells, ensuring a state of homeostasis.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 13, Verse 17):</strong></h2><p>“अविभक्तं च भूतेषु विभक्तमिव च स्थितम् | भूतभर्तृ च तज्ज्ञेयं ग्रसिष्णु प्रभविष्णु च ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;He is indivisible, yet appears as if divided in beings. He is to be understood as the sustainer of all, the devourer and also the creator.&#8221;</p><p>May you harness the miraculous healing power of the mitochondria, uniting it with the eternal spirit within, to walk a path of boundless energy and vitality.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">894</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Healing power of mother</title>
		<link>/healing-power-of-mother/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls who have been cradled by the nurturing embrace of the universe 🌺, The essence of a]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls who have been cradled by the nurturing embrace of the universe <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>The essence of a mother, beloved seekers, is the very embodiment of nature&#8217;s boundless compassion, profound wisdom, and unwavering love. She is the healing balm for every wound, the shelter from every storm, and the beacon that guides us through life&#8217;s mazes.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita, in its vast reservoir of wisdom, extols: &#8216;All beings are born from the womb of prakriti (nature, often likened to a mother); and I am the seed-giving father.&#8217; This reflects the cosmic interplay of divine energies, reminding us of the universal motherly force that continually nurtures and supports.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s deeply reflect on this profound relationship:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Rhythms</strong>: Just as a mother instinctively knows the needs of her child, nature too operates in harmonious rhythms, providing sustenance, healing, and rejuvenation.</li>

<li><strong>Sacred Bond</strong>: The bond between a child and a mother transcends the physical realm. It is a divine connection, an umbilical cord of spiritual energy, which remains unbroken through life&#8217;s tribulations.</li>

<li><strong>Cradle of Healing</strong>: A mother&#8217;s lap, her soothing words, and her gentle touch have the miraculous power to heal the deepest of wounds, both physical and emotional. She is the reservoir of strength in moments of weakness, the solace in times of distress.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 9, Verse 18):</strong></h2><p>“गतिर्भर्ता प्रभुः साक्षी निवासः शरणं सुहृत् | प्रभवः प्रलयः स्थानं निधानं बीजमव्ययम् ||”</p><p>Which means:</p><p>&#8220;I am the goal, the sustainer, the master, the witness, the abode, the refuge, and the most dear friend. I am the creation and the annihilation, the basis of everything, the resting place and the eternal seed.&#8221;</p><p>May your journey through life be forever blessed by the healing power of the mother, in all her forms, guiding you towards wholeness and harmony.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">891</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the significance of the True Guru&#8217;s role?What is the significance of the True Guru&#8217;s role?What is the significance of the True Guru&#8217;s role?</title>
		<link>/what-is-the-significance-of-the-true-gurus-rolewhat-is-the-significance-of-the-true-gurus-rolewhat-is-the-significance-of-the-true-gurus-role/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the sincere seekers on the path of self-realisation 🌺, The role of a True Guru is akin to the]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the sincere seekers on the path of self-realisation <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>The role of a True Guru is akin to the lighthouse guiding ships through the darkest nights and tumultuous seas. The Guru does not just impart knowledge but illuminates the very soul, dispelling the shadows of ignorance and doubt.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita, in its profound wisdom, speaks of the importance of such guidance: <em>&#8216;Acquire knowledge through reverence to those who perceive the truth, bow to them, and inquire sincerely. Those seers of truth will teach you knowledge.&#8217;</em></p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let us delve into the sacred role of a True Guru:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Guiding Light</strong>: The Guru offers direction, showing the spiritual aspirant the path, even when it remains veiled by worldly distractions or inner turmoil.</li>

<li><strong>Mirror to the Soul</strong>: Through their wisdom and insight, the Guru reflects the seeker&#8217;s true self, revealing both their latent potential and areas of growth.</li>

<li><strong>Anchor in Storms</strong>: When doubts arise or faith wavers, the Guru stands firm as an anchor, offering stability and clarity amidst life&#8217;s tempests.</li>

<li><strong>Bridge to the Divine</strong>: The Guru not only talks of the Divine but serves as a living bridge, enabling the disciple to experience and connect with that transcendent reality.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the boundless ocean of the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 4, Verse 34):</strong></h2><p><em>“तद्विद्धि प्रणिपातेन परिप्रश्नेन सेवया | उपदेक्ष्यन्ति ते ज्ञानं ज्ञानिनस्तत्त्वदर्शिनः ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;Know that through prostration, inquiry, and service, the wise who have realized the truth will impart knowledge unto you.&#8221;</em></p><p>May each one find their guiding light, their True Guru, who leads them from darkness to luminance, from untruth to truth.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to discover the path to inner strength?</title>
		<link>/how-to-discover-the-path-to-inner-strength/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=854</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the diligent souls striving for deeper meaning and strength 🌺, Inner strength, revered ones, is not just an attribute]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the diligent souls striving for deeper meaning and strength <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Inner strength, revered ones, is not just an attribute but the very bedrock of our existence. It&#8217;s the silent force that anchors us amidst the fiercest storms and illuminates our path in the darkest nights.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates: <em>&#8216;For those who have conquered the mind, it is their friend. For those who have failed to do so, the mind is their enemy.&#8217;</em> Mastery over one&#8217;s mind is the first step toward harnessing inner strength.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Discover this transformative power:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Self-Reflection</strong>: Dive deep within, seeking the still waters of your soul. It is here, in introspection, that the pearls of wisdom and strength reside.</li>

<li><strong>Discipline &amp; Dedication</strong>: Through consistent practice and devotion, channel the boundless energy within. Harness it to reinforce your resolve and resilience.</li>

<li><strong>Nourish the Soul</strong>: Engage in spiritual rituals, meditations, and acts of selfless service. These are the wellsprings from which inner fortitude is replenished and refined.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the heart of the Shrimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 18, Verse 58):</strong></h2><p><em>“मच्चित्तः सर्वदुर्गाणि मत्प्रसादात्तरिष्यसि | अथ चेत्त्वमहङ्कारान्न श्रोष्यसि विनङ्क्ष्यसि ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;If you become conscious of Me, you will pass over all the obstacles of conditioned life by My grace. If, however, you do not work in such consciousness but act through false ego, not hearing Me, you will be lost.&#8221;</em></p><p>May your journey within unveil the reservoir of strength that has always been yours, waiting just beneath the surface of consciousness.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">854</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to do when things get stuck?</title>
		<link>/what-to-do-when-things-get-stuck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the noble souls, seeking clarity amidst life&#8217;s maze 🌺, In our grand journey of existence, there come phases where]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the noble souls, seeking clarity amidst life&#8217;s maze <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>In our grand journey of existence, there come phases where the wheels of progress seem to halt, where the path ahead appears blurred. But remember, dear seekers, every pause is an opportunity for reflection and growth.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita teaches: <em>&#8216;Change is the law of the universe. What you think of as death is indeed life.&#8217;</em> Times of stagnation, if perceived rightly, can be the harbingers of a new dawn.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In moments of standstill:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Deep Reflection</strong>: Use this period to introspect. Revisit your goals, realign with your purpose, and ensure your heart and soul are in harmony with your aspirations.</li>

<li><strong>Unwavering Faith</strong>: The cosmic play is vast and complex. Trust the divine orchestration. Believe that even in stillness, the universe is conspiring for your highest good.</li>

<li><strong>Engage in Svadhyaya</strong>: Delve into self-study and spiritual readings. Often, wisdom from sacred texts and teachings can provide the illumination needed to see through the fog of uncertainty.</li>

<li><strong>Seek Guidance</strong>: Turn to wise mentors, sages, and the community. Sharing your journey and seeking counsel can pave the way for fresh perspectives and insights.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 18, Verse 58):</strong></h2><p><em>“मच्चित्तः सर्वदुर्गाणि मत्प्रसादात्तरिष्यसि | अथ चेत्त्वमहंकारान्न श्रोष्यसि विनंक्ष्यसि ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;If you become conscious of Me, you will pass over all obstacles by My grace. But if you act out of false ego, not listening to Me, you will be lost.&#8221;</em></p><p>When paths are obscured and progress seems distant, let faith be your guide and wisdom your compass.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33c.png" alt="🌼" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">848</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to embrace and overcome setbacks with grace?</title>
		<link>/how-to-embrace-and-overcome-setbacks-with-grace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the valiant hearts striving in the grand theatre of existence 🌺, Failure, beloved seekers, is but a fleeting shadow]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the valiant hearts striving in the grand theatre of existence <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Failure, beloved seekers, is but a fleeting shadow on the canvas of life. It is not a testament to one&#8217;s worth, but a teacher clothed in lessons of humility, perseverance, and resilience.</p><p><strong>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elegantly states: </strong><strong><em>&#8216;</em></strong><em>We have control over our actions, but no command over the results of those actions.&#8217;</em> In recognizing this, we understand that while efforts are our domain, outcomes are orchestrated by the cosmos.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Wisdom to navigate the labyrinth of failure:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Celebrate Effort</strong>: In every endeavour, honour the dedication, sincerity, and intention you poured into it. Recognize that every step, regardless of its outcome, is a triumph of spirit.</li>

<li><strong>Embrace Growth</strong>: Failure offers invaluable insights. It is an opportunity for reflection, understanding, and growth. By learning from setbacks, we refine our path and approach.</li>

<li><strong>Resilient Spirit</strong>: Each stumble is an invitation to rise with greater vigor and clarity. Let your spirit not be dampened by setbacks but ignited by the promise of new beginnings.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the treasure trove of the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 18, Verse 66):</strong></h2><p><em>“सर्वधर्मान्परित्यज्य मामेकं शरणं व्रज | अहं त्वां सर्वपापेभ्यो मोक्षयिष्यामि मा शुचः ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;Abandon all paths, all virtues, and surrender exclusively unto me. I will deliver you from all sinful reactions. Do not despair.&#8221;</em></p><p>May you perceive failure not as an end, but as a bend in the journey, leading you to horizons yet unexplored and potential yet untapped.</p><p>Continued blessings…<br><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33c.png" alt="🌼" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">845</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why does the mind wander from its focus?</title>
		<link>/why-does-the-mind-wander-from-its-focus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the earnest seekers of truth and clarity 🌺, Distraction, dear souls, can be likened to the fluttering leaves caught]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the earnest seekers of truth and clarity <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Distraction, dear souls, can be likened to the fluttering leaves caught in a gust of wind, taken away from their place of stillness. Just as these leaves drift without anchor, a distracted mind floats aimlessly amidst the vast oceans of external stimuli.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita expounds: <em>&#8216;For one who has conquered the mind, the mind is the best of friends; but for one who has failed to do so, the mind will remain the greatest enemy.&#8217;</em> When the mind isn&#8217;t anchored in purpose and awareness, it becomes susceptible to external allurements.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Delve deeper into the roots of distraction:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>The Play of the Senses</strong>: Our senses are like five horses drawing the chariot of life. Unrestrained, they can pull us in myriad directions, away from our true path.</li>

<li><strong>Seeking External Validation</strong>: In today&#8217;s interconnected world, many seek validation from outside. This external focus scatters the mind, leading it away from inner equilibrium.</li>

<li><strong>Lack of Purpose</strong>: A mind without a guiding purpose or objective is like a ship without a compass. It becomes vulnerable to the waves of whims and fancies.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>To centre the mind and dissolve distraction, the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 6, Verse 26) guides:</strong></h2><p><em>“यतो यतो निश्चलति मनश्चंचलमस्थिरम् | ततस्ततो नियम्यैतदात्मन्येव वशं नयेत् ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;Wherever the restless and unsteady mind wanders, one should bring it back and continually focus it on the Self.&#8221;</em></p><p>In harnessing the mind&#8217;s energy and directing it purposefully, we not only minimise distractions but also realise our highest potential.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">842</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shri Vishnu Stuti &#8211; A Deep Dive into the Ocean of Devotion</title>
		<link>/shri-vishnu-stuti-a-deep-dive-into-the-ocean-of-devotion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sacred Verses Unveiled]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introduction Welcome, dear soul, to the sacred sanctuary where every word penned down is a petal offered at the lotus]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Introduction</h3><p>Welcome, dear soul, to the sacred sanctuary where every word penned down is a petal offered at the lotus feet of the Divine. Today, we start our elevating journey through the resplendent verses of &#8220;<strong>Shri Vishnu Stuti.</strong>&#8221; This eternal divine hymn serves as both a celebration and invocation of <strong>God Shri Vishnu</strong>, the <strong>Preserver</strong> in the Divine Trinity. Each verse, a woven garland of Sanskrit syllables, carries the aroma of timeless devotion and infinite wisdom. Let these words not just be read but be absorbed, so they echo in the inner corridors of your heart, where God Shri Vishnu resides.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading">Vishnu Stuti &#8211; Vishnushodashanamani Meaning with Interpretation by Sri Guru Vyas</h2><h3 class="wp-block-heading">First Section: Invocation for Removing Obstacles</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio">शुक्लाम्बरधरं विष्णुं शशिवर्णं चतुर्भुजम्,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio">प्रसन्नवदनं ध्यायेत् सर्वविघ्नोपशान्तये।</h4></blockquote><p>In this opening verse, the divine form of God Shri Vishnu is presented as wearing pure white garments, signifying purity and holiness. His complexion shines like the moon, embodying tranquility. With four arms, he holds the power to protect us in all directions. His face wears an eternally joyous smile, giving us reassurance. By meditating on this divine form, all obstacles and challenges in life will be erased. This verse sets the tone for beginning any endeavor without hindrances.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Second Section: Attributes of God Shri Vishnu</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">शान्ताकारं भुजगशयनं पद्मनाभं सुरेशं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">विश्वाधारं गगनसदृशं मेघवर्ण शुभाङ्गम्।</h4></blockquote><p>Here, we delve deeper into the qualities and grandeur of God Shri Vishnu. His form is peaceful, embodying the essence of tranquility that can soothe any troubled heart. He reclines on the serpent Adi Shesha, representing the universe&#8217;s unending cycles of creation and dissolution. His navel blooms a lotus, the eternal source of all creation. As the Lord of lords, he governs the cosmic laws. His expansive form is limitless like the sky. The color of his skin resembles a dark rain cloud, emphasizing the life-giving and sustaining aspects of his divinity.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Third Section: God Shri Vishnu in Daily Life</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">औषधे चिंतये विष्णुम भोजने च जनार्धनम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">शयने पद्मनाभं च विवाहे च प्रजापतिम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">युद्धे चक्रधरम देवं प्रवासे च त्रिविक्रमं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">नारायणं तनु त्यागे श्रीधरं प्रिय संगमे,</h4></blockquote><p>The shloka urges us to remember God Shri Vishnu throughout various moments in our daily life. When taking medicine, think of him as the healer. While eating, remember him as the sustainer. At bedtime, see him as the comforter. During marriage, he is the eternal matchmaker. In battle, he&#8217;s our protector. During travel, he&#8217;s the guide. In the face of death, he&#8217;s the eternal soul. And in times of love and unity, he is the embodiment of all relationships.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Fourth Section: God Shri Vishnu in Challenges</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">दुःस्वप्ने स्मर गोविन्दम संकटे मधुसूधनम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">कानने नारासिम्हम च पावके जलाशयिनाम,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">जलमध्ये वराहम च पर्वते रघु नन्दनं,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">गमने वामनं चैव सर्व कार्येशु माधवं।</h4></blockquote><p>In times of distress or trouble, each form of God Shri Vishnu comes as a guide, a savior, or a protector. Whether it&#8217;s a bad dream, life challenges, dangerous forests, or perils by fire, each avatar has a specific role. Remembering these forms in specific circumstances can offer comfort and solutions.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">Final Section: The Fruit of Devotion</h3><blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><h4 class="wp-block-heading">षोडशैतानी नमानी प्रातरुत्थाय यह पठेत,</h4>

<h4 class="wp-block-heading">सर्वपापा विर्निमुक्तो विष्णुलोके महीयते।</h4></blockquote><p>Reciting these sixteen names of God Shri Vishnu early in the morning washes away all sins and bestows a high place in Vishnuloka, his eternal abode.</p><p>Incorporate these verses into your daily life. Each time you chant or even think of them, it&#8217;s like sending a personal invitation to God Shri Vishnu to walk alongside you. And what&#8217;s more reassuring than knowing the divine is by your side, guiding, protecting, and loving you in every moment of life?</p><figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Vishnustuti- Vishnushodashanamani" width="500" height="375" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kRPMyg1xhCA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>This hymn is not merely a combination of words and syllables but an intimate conversation between you and the Divine.</strong></h2><p><strong>It serves as a lighthouse guiding you through the murky waters of life&#8217;s challenges, illuminating your path with the divine glow of God Shri Vishnu&#8217;s love, wisdom, and protection.</strong> </p><p>May your life be filled with the boundless grace of God Shri Vishnu, and may you find solace, strength, and eternal joy in these divine verses. Here, your diary closes, but the dialogue with the Divine continues forever. With a heart full of devotion and a soul touched by the divine, walk forth in life, knowing that you&#8217;re never alone; for in every step, God Shri Vishnu walks with you.</p><p>&#8211; <strong>Sri Guru Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society,<br>Jodhpur (Rajasthan) &#8211; 342003</p><p></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1486</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
