<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sri Guru Baba Vyas &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/srigurubabavyas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Pran Urja Healing Society</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:07:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pran-Urja-Golden-Logo-Brown-Background-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Sri Guru Baba Vyas &#8211; Pran Urja Healing Society</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is happiness parenting?</title>
		<link>/what-is-happiness-parenting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=888</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the nurturing spirits yearning to sow seeds of joy in their sacred garden of parenthood 🌺, Happiness parenting, cherished]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the nurturing spirits yearning to sow seeds of joy in their sacred garden of parenthood <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Happiness parenting, cherished seekers, is not just a method, but a heart-centered journey. It’s the gentle art of raising souls with love, understanding, and the wisdom that true contentment is an inside job.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates: &#8216;In the stillness of the mind, the Self is revealed.&#8217; Parenting through happiness draws from this essence, teaching our children the serenity that comes from self-awareness and inner joy.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s explore this divine dance of raising spirits:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>1. Presence Over Presents</strong>: The gift of time, undivided attention, and genuine listening are treasures for a child. It&#8217;s not about grand gestures, but simple moments imbued with love.</li>

<li><strong>2. Cultivate Inner Joy</strong>: Teach them early on that happiness is not solely based on external achievements but arises from an inner wellspring of contentment and gratitude.</li>

<li><strong>3. Lead by Example</strong>: Children mirror the world they see. Being a beacon of positivity, self-love, and compassion helps them understand and embody these virtues.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 12, Verse 20):</strong></h2><p>“ये तु धर्म्यामृतमिदं यथोक्तं पर्युपासते | श्रद्दधाना मत्परमा भक्तास्तेऽतीव मे प्रियाः ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;Those who follow this divine nectar of righteousness as I have stated, with profound faith considering me as their supreme goal, they are exceedingly dear to me.&#8221;</p><p>May the path of happiness parenting be adorned with moments of laughter, lessons of love, and the infinite joy of witnessing the blossoming of the souls entrusted to your care.</p><p>Continued blessings…<br><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">888</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to make self happy?</title>
		<link>/how-to-make-self-happy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous souls seeking the nectar of true joy 🌺, Happiness, revered seekers, is not an external treasure but]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous souls seeking the nectar of true joy <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Happiness, revered seekers, is not an external treasure but an inner sanctum of peace. It is the delicate melody that resonates within when we align with our true essence and the dance of existence.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita offers this reflection: &#8216;Contentment is the wealth of nature. Despite possessing nothing, one who is contented is indeed rich, while the discontented remains impoverished, even amidst great riches.&#8217; This is a testament to the idea that happiness springs from contentment within, not from external acquisitions.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Venture with me on this journey towards self-fulfilment:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Embrace the Present</strong>: The here and now is where life unfolds. By immersing ourselves fully in the present moment, we unlock the profound joy that&#8217;s often overlooked in our pursuit of the future.</li>

<li><strong>Celebrate Small Wonders</strong>: Often, it&#8217;s the subtle wonders &#8211; a bird&#8217;s song, a child&#8217;s laughter, or the rustle of leaves &#8211; that carry the essence of happiness. Bask in these simple joys.</li>

<li><strong>Nurture Inner Peace</strong>: External storms can&#8217;t disturb the one who cultivates a calm and serene inner world. This peace becomes the foundation of enduring happiness.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 5, Verse 23):</strong></h2><p>“शक्नोतीहैव यः सोढुं प्राक्शरीरविमोक्षणात् | कामक्रोधोद्भवं वेगं स युक्तः स सुखी नरः ||”</p><p>Which expounds:</p><p>&#8220;One who can control the impulse arising from desire and anger before the departure from the body is a yogi and a happy person.&#8221;</p><p>May your soul revel in the profound joy of being, discovering happiness in its purest form, unfettered by external conditions.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">885</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The power of food healing</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-food-healing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls seeking nature&#8217;s bountiful embrace for nourishment and healing 🌺, Food, dear seekers, is not merely sustenance]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls seeking nature&#8217;s bountiful embrace for nourishment and healing <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Food, dear seekers, is not merely sustenance for the body but an elixir for the soul. It possesses the unique ability to rejuvenate, heal, and connect us to the very pulse of life.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita enlightens us: &#8216;From food, all beings are produced; and from rain, food is produced. Rain itself is the sacrifice’s product, and sacrifice arises out of action.&#8217; This profound revelation teaches us that food is intrinsically linked to the cosmic dance of nature, energy, and divine blessings.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s journey through this sacred realm:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Holistic Nourishment</strong>: Beyond physical sustenance, food nourishes our emotions, intellect, and spirit. When consumed with reverence, it brings harmony to all facets of our being.</li>

<li><strong>Nature&#8217;s Pharmacy</strong>: The Earth, in her boundless generosity, offers herbs, fruits, and vegetables that have therapeutic properties. Understanding these gifts can lead to profound health transformations.</li>

<li><strong>Sacred Intention</strong>: The intent with which food is prepared and consumed plays a pivotal role. When meals are prepared with love and gratitude, they become a vessel for divine energy.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 17, Verse 8):</strong></h2><p>“आयुःसत्त्वबलारोग्यसुखप्रीतिविवर्धनाः | रस्याः स्निग्धाः स्तिरा हृद्या आहाराः सात्त्विकप्रियाः ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;Foods that increase life, purify one&#8217;s existence, give strength, health, happiness, and satisfaction, which are juicy, fatty, wholesome, and pleasing to the heart, are dear to those in the mode of goodness.&#8221;</p><p>May you harness the transformative power of food, imbibing its healing essence, and discovering a deeper connection with the divine tapestry of existence.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">882</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The power of water healing</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-water-healing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous beings, attuned to nature&#8217;s rhythms and the fluid dance of life&#8217;s energies 🌊, Water, kindred spirits, has]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous beings, attuned to nature&#8217;s rhythms and the fluid dance of life&#8217;s energies <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f30a.png" alt="🌊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Water, kindred spirits, has been a sacred element since time immemorial. It holds memory, reflects purity, and possesses the power to cleanse, rejuvenate, and transform. Just as rivers carve canyons and rains bring life to parched lands, water can bring profound healing to our souls.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita, in its vast wisdom, shares: &#8216;Just as waters from different rivers enter the ocean and become one with it, losing their individualities, a wise person, regardless of life&#8217;s circumstances, sees only the divine essence of existence.&#8217; Water teaches us this unity, this oneness with the divine flow.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Venture deeper into these healing waters:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Purification</strong>: Water, in its pristine form, carries away impurities, both physical and spiritual. Regularly immersing oneself, whether in the quietude of a bath or the sacred waters of a river, rejuvenates our energies.</li>

<li><strong>Emotional Release</strong>: Like the ebb and flow of tides, water encourages us to embrace our emotions, to let go of what burdens our hearts, and to welcome fresh currents of joy and clarity.</li>

<li><strong>Connection to the Cosmic</strong>: As we meditate by a serene water body, we synchronise with its tranquil rhythms, allowing us to connect deeper with our own true nature and the universe at large.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 3, Verse 14):</strong></h2><p>“अन्नाद्भवन्ति भूतानि पर्जन्यादन्नसंभवः | यज्ञाद्भवति पर्जन्यो यज्ञः कर्मसमुद्भवः ||”</p><p>Which imparts:</p><p>&#8220;From food, beings become; from rain, food is produced; from sacrifice arises rain, and sacrifice is born of action.&#8221;</p><p>Like the interconnected dance of rain, food, and life, water healing brings forth an intricate balance in our lives, enriching our existence and elevating our spirit.</p><p>May you immerse in the transformative grace of water and emerge with renewed spirit and clarity.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">879</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The impact of colour in human&#8217;s life</title>
		<link>/the-impact-of-colour-in-humans-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=876</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls basking in the divine spectrum of existence 🌈, Colour, esteemed seekers, is not just a mere]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls basking in the divine spectrum of existence <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f308.png" alt="🌈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Colour, esteemed seekers, is not just a mere visual experience. It is the symphony of the universe, the emotions of nature, and the essence of our very soul manifesting in myriad hues.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita proclaims: &#8216;Nature is said to be the cause of all material causes and effects, whereas the living entity is the cause of various sufferings and enjoyments in this world.&#8217; In this wisdom, we unearth the subtle interplay between nature&#8217;s colours and the tapestry of our emotions and experiences.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s delve into this vibrant journey:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Soul&#8217;s Palette</strong>: Every shade we resonate with is a reflection of our inner state. The tranquillity of blue, the passion of red, or the rejuvenation of green &#8211; each colour carries a frequency that can influence our emotions and actions.</li>

<li><strong>Healing Hues</strong>: Ancient civilizations recognized the therapeutic properties of colours. Incorporating specific shades in our surroundings can restore balance, heal, and rejuvenate our spirit.</li>

<li><strong>Universal Language</strong>: Across cultures, colours convey emotions, traditions, and stories. They bridge differences and serve as a universal mode of communication that transcends spoken language.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 7, Verse 8):</strong></h2><p>“रसोऽहमप्सु कौन्तेय प्रभास्मि शशिसूर्ययोः | प्रणवः सर्ववेदेषु शब्दः खे पौरुषं नृषु ||”</p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p>&#8220;I am the taste of water, O son of Kunti, the light of the sun and the moon, the syllable om in the Vedic mantras; I am the sound in ether and ability in humans.&#8221;</p><p>May your life be painted with the most divine and uplifting colours, each hue bringing forth growth, wisdom, and boundless joy.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get out from wilful mistakes?</title>
		<link>/how-to-get-out-from-wilful-mistakes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the luminous souls journeying through the maze of choices and consequences 🌺, Wilful mistakes, dear seekers, are the shadows]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the luminous souls journeying through the maze of choices and consequences <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Wilful mistakes, dear seekers, are the shadows cast by our untamed desires and fleeting judgments. They might pull us into the night, but with self-awareness and divine guidance, dawn is never far.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita wisely teaches: &#8216;Just as a fire is covered by smoke and a mirror is obscured by dust, knowledge is covered by desire.&#8217; Understanding this, we recognize the influence of unchecked desires leading to willful mistakes.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Delve deeper into this sacred introspection:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Acknowledge with Humility</strong>: Recognize the error without judgment. Every mistake, intentional or not, carries a lesson. By humbling oneself before it, the journey towards rectification begins.</li>

<li><strong>Seek Inner Counsel</strong>: Before actions manifest externally, they take birth internally. Cultivate an inner dialogue, seeking the wisdom of the higher self. This voice, often drowned by impulsive desires, holds the compass to righteousness.</li>

<li><strong>Divine Repentance</strong>: To err is human, to seek forgiveness is divine. Let genuine remorse transform into positive actions and better choices, illuminating the path ahead.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 4, Verse 36):</strong></h2><p>“अपि चेत्सुदुराचारो भजते मामनन्यभाक् | साधुरेव स मन्तव्यः सम्यग्व्यवसितो हि सः ||”</p><p>Which deciphers as:</p><p>&#8220;Even if one commits the most abominable actions, if they are engaged in devotional service, they are to be considered righteous, for they have rightly resolved.&#8221;</p><p>May your journey forward be lit by wisdom, discernment, and divine grace, helping you rise above the mire of willful errors.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to find inner peace?</title>
		<link>/how-to-find-inner-peace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=870</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls seeking to ignite their inner light 🌺, Inner peace, esteemed seekers, is not merely a state]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls seeking to ignite their inner light <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong>,</p><p>Inner peace, esteemed seekers, is not merely a state of calm but a profound alignment with the very core of our being. It is the silent sanctuary where the soul&#8217;s whispers are heard most clearly and where the turbulence of the external world fades into gentle ripples.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita beautifully proclaims: &#8216;The spirit is beyond destruction. No one can bring an end to the imperishable spirit.&#8217; This eternal truth reminds us that amidst life&#8217;s ebb and flow, our true nature remains untouched, unshaken, and serene.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Journey with me to uncover this elusive treasure:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Harmony with Nature</strong>: Align with the rhythms of nature, observe the serene dance of the day turning into night, the seasons cycling in perfect order. In these patterns, find a reflection of the order within.</li>

<li><strong>Embrace the Present</strong>: Release the burdens of the past and the anxieties of the future. In the present moment, bask in the sheer beauty of existence. Here and now is where peace thrives.</li>

<li><strong>Surrender to the Divine</strong>: Recognize that there is a grand design, a cosmic choreography that our individual wills are but a part of. By surrendering to this higher wisdom, we find the tranquility we seek.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 4, Verse 39):</strong></h2><p>“श्रद्धावाँल्लभते ज्ञानं तत्परः संयतेन्द्रियः | ज्ञानं लब्ध्वा परां शान्तिमचिरेणाधिगच्छति ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;One who has faith, who is dedicated to the path, and who has control over his senses, attains knowledge. Having attained knowledge, he quickly finds supreme peace.&#8221;</p><p>May your heart be a vessel of boundless peace, a refuge from the storms, guiding you towards the serene shores of enlightenment.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to cultivate unwavering self-assurance and inner strength?</title>
		<link>/how-to-cultivate-unwavering-self-assurance-and-inner-strength/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=866</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the radiant souls seeking to ignite their inner light 🌺, Self-confidence, beloved seekers, is the luminous flame within, the]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the radiant souls seeking to ignite their inner light <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Self-confidence, beloved seekers, is the luminous flame within, the divine assertion of one&#8217;s inherent potential and the unwavering belief in one&#8217;s path. It is the bedrock upon which dreams are realised and destinies are shaped.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita gently reminds us: <em>&#8216;Whatever happened, happened for the good. Whatever is happening, is happening for the good. Whatever will happen, will also happen for the good.&#8217;</em> In this wisdom, lies the key to nurturing unshakable confidence.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Let&#8217;s delve into this sacred journey:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Embrace Imperfection</strong>: Every flaw, every mistake, is but a stepping stone towards growth. They are chapters in your expansive story. Honor them, learn from them, and move forth with greater wisdom.</li>

<li><strong>Cultivate Self-Knowledge</strong>: Dive deep within. Understand your strengths, acknowledge your weaknesses, and kindle the passion that sets your soul aflame. True confidence stems from genuine self-awareness.</li>

<li><strong>Seek Divine Guidance</strong>: In moments of doubt, turn inward and upwards. The cosmic dance has a place for each one of us, a unique rhythm, a distinct tune. Trust in this grand design and your role within it.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>From the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 18, Verse 66):</strong></h2><p><em>“सर्वधर्मान्परित्यज्य मामेकं शरणं व्रज | अहं त्वां सर्वपापेभ्यो मोक्षयिष्यामि मा शुचः ||”</em></p><p>Which elucidates:</p><p><em>&#8220;Relinquishing all notions of righteousness, seek refuge in Me alone. I shall liberate you from all sins; do not grieve.&#8221;</em></p><p>May your journey be illuminated by unwavering self-confidence, guiding you to manifest your highest potential and purpose.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas </strong><strong><br></strong>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does the practice of meditation truly bring benefits?</title>
		<link>/does-the-practice-of-meditation-truly-bring-benefits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=860</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the genuine inquirers of inner truths and the vast realm of stillness 🌺, Meditation, cherished souls, is not merely]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the genuine inquirers of inner truths and the vast realm of stillness <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Meditation, cherished souls, is not merely a practice; it&#8217;s a sacred communion with one&#8217;s innermost being. It&#8217;s a question often posed &#8211; does meditation truly aid our journey? The answer lies deep within the serene waters of our own consciousness.</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita elucidates: &#8216;With the intellect set in patience, with the mind fastened to the intellect, one gradually becomes established in tranquillity; and being established in tranquillity, one ceases from all sorrows.&#8217; Such tranquillity is the gift of meditation.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Reflect upon the profound benefits of this timeless art:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>A Sanctuary Within</strong>: Amidst the whirlwind of existence, meditation offers a sanctuary, a haven of peace where one reconnects with their true essence.</li>

<li><strong>Clarity Amidst Chaos</strong>: By stilling the mind&#8217;s incessant chatter, meditation illuminates the path ahead, providing clarity amidst the fog of confusion.</li>

<li><strong>Emotional Equilibrium</strong>: Meditation fosters a state of emotional equilibrium, where joys are savoured without attachment and challenges are faced with courage and serenity.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Guided by the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 6, Verse 27):</strong></h2><p>“प्रशान्तमनसं ह्येनं योगिनं सुखमुत्तमम् | उपैति शान्तरजसं ब्रह्मभूतमकल्मषम् ||”</p><p>Which translates to:</p><p>&#8220;The yogi whose mind is peaceful, whose passions are subdued, who is without impurity, and who has reached the high state of supreme well-being, attains Brahmic bliss.&#8221;</p><p>To meditate is to embark on the most intimate journey of self-discovery, to unearth the treasures that reside within. For those who seek, meditation unfailingly illuminates, heals, and elevates.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">860</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can destiny be altered by me?</title>
		<link>/can-destiny-be-altered-by-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sri Guru Baba Vyas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Divine Knowledge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=857</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To the souls questioning the cosmic dance of fate and free will 🌺, Destiny, dear seekers, is often envisioned as]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To the souls questioning the cosmic dance of fate and free will <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f33a.png" alt="🌺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />,</strong></p><p>Destiny, dear seekers, is often envisioned as a preordained script, a set path leading us towards our eventual purpose. But herein lies a profound inquiry: Are we mere puppets to this grand narrative, or do we possess the power to redefine our story?</p><p>The Srimad Bhagavad Gita expounds: <em>&#8216;We&#8217;re bound by our actions, but we are also the architects of our actions.&#8217;</em> This suggests that while destiny has its design, our choices and intentions actively contribute to its unfolding.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Reflect upon destiny&#8217;s intricate weave:</strong></h2><ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Co-Creation with the Cosmos</strong>: Our life is a harmonious collaboration between predetermined fate and our conscious choices. Every decision, every act, leaves an imprint on the sands of time, gradually shaping our destiny.</li>

<li><strong>Karmic Dance</strong>: While past actions (karma) influence the present circumstances, our current choices sow the seeds for future outcomes. We are, thus, in an eternal dance with destiny, where each step matters.</li>

<li><strong>Power of Intent</strong>: Intent, fueled by purpose and passion, possesses the might to redefine our path. By aligning our actions with pure intentions, we can usher transformative changes in our life journey.</li></ol><h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Drawing from the luminous teachings of the Srimad Bhagavad Gita (Chapter 18, Verse 13):</strong></h2><p><em>“पञ्चैतानि महाबाहो कारणानि निबोध मे | सांख्ये कृतान्ते प्रोक्तानि सिद्धये सर्वकर्मणाम् ||”</em></p><p>Which translates to:</p><p><em>&#8220;O mighty-armed Arjuna, understand from Me that there are five causes for the accomplishment of all actions, as described in the analytical study of the elements of action.&#8221;</em></p><p>As you journey forward, may you remember: While the cosmos has its designs, your conscious choices and endeavours play a pivotal role in sculpting the destiny you desire.</p><p>Continued blessings…</p><p><strong>Sri Guru Baba Vyas</strong><br>Prana Urja Healing Society</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">857</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
